But isn't there something to be said for the fact that a lot of cats end up in these crime spaces because of lack of access to industry, right?
Industry resources?
Lack of access to resources, et cetera.
I know.
And it's hard to have that conversation with some people because I always had this conversation.
I'm like, look, if some of our folks think that black people run a drug game, I'm like, look, I got a moon to sell your ass to.
Like, it's not happening.
At best, you're going to be a Walmart district manager.
That's it.
Like, that's it.
Basically, all you're doing all day is standing and saying, welcome to Walmart.
Corner boys.
And now we just have to get to them in a different way.
Most people don't want to live like that.
And it's a hard thing for some people to grapple.
Even our folks who have been beat down on with this media drum for all these years, that young black people only want to do these things and they only want to be involved in crime.
It used to be solely young black men.
Now, increasingly, they're like, look at the young black girls.
They're out here shooting.
And we have to break through that and understand that that's a purposeful thing that folks are doing to try to keep us divided.